<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="kitePageDesignerFeature"
      label="Kite Page Designer Feature"
      version="1.0.11"
      provider-name="Lucid Bilgisayar Hiz. Dan. San. ve Tic. Ltd. Şti.">

   <description url="http://www.lucidcode.com.tr">
      Feature Includes:
- Eclipse Perspective for Kite development environment.
- Eclipse MultiPage Editor for editing Kite Framework pages.
- Eclipse New Project Wizard for Kite Project Maven Archetype.
- New Project Wizard for Kite Framework projects.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.lucidcode.com.tr">
      Kite Framework Page Designer Feature Copyright Notice
3-May-2014 
Copyright Lucid Bilgisayar Hiz. Dan. San. ve Tic. Ltd. Şti. 2014
www.lucidcode.com.tr 
COPYRIGHT 
All title and copyrights in and to Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature (including but not limited to any images and text incorporated
into or supplied with Kite Framework Page Designer Feature),
all and any copies of Kite Framework Page Designer Feature are
owned by the Author of this Software. Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature is protected by copyright laws and international treaty
provisions. Therefore, you must treat Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature like any other copyrighted material. 
WARRANTY 
The Author of this Software expressly disclaims any warranty
for Kite Framework Page Designer Feature. Kite Framework Page
Designer Feature and any related documentation is provided &quot;as
is&quot; without warranty of any kind, either express or implied,
including, without limitation, the implied warranties or 
merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non infringement.
The entire risk arising out of use of Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature remains with the purchaser. 
LIABILITY 
In no event shall Lucid Bilgisayar Hiz. Dan. San. ve Tic. Ltd.
Şti. or the author of this Software be liable for any damages
whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of
business profits, business interruption, loss of business information,
or any other financial loss) arising out of the use of or inability
to use Kite Framework Page Designer Feature, even if the Author
of this Software has been advised of the possibility of such
damages.
SOFTWARE UPGRADES 
This licence grants the purchaser the right to free upgrades
as they become available.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.lucidcode.com.tr">
      Kite Framework Page Designer Feature Commercial Licence 
3-May-2014 
Copyright Lucid Bilgisayar Hiz. Dan. San. ve Tic. Ltd. Şti. 2014
www.lucidcode.com.tr 
END-USER LICENCE AGREEMENT 
This End-User Licence Agreement is a legal agreement between
you (an individual or a single entity) and the 
author of this software for the software product Kite Framework
Page Designer Feature. By installing, copying, or otherwise using
Kite Framework Page Designer Feature, you agree to be bound by
the terms of this Licence. If you do not agree to the terms of
this Licence do not install or use Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature. 
PRODUCT LICENCE 
Kite Framework Page Designer Feature is protected by copyright
laws and international copyright treaties, as well as other intellectual
property laws and treaties. Kite Framework Page Designer Feature
is Licenced, and sold. The definition of Kite Framework Page
Designer Feature includes any files generated by Kite Framework
Page Designer Feature, such as log files and any electronic documentation.
No attempt shall be made to reverse engineer Kite Framework Page
Designer Feature. 
GRANT OF LICENCE 
This Licence grants you the right to install and use Kite Framework
Page Designer Feature for commercial and personal use. You may
not sell for profit or distribute Kite Framework Page Designer
Feature without first obtaining a licence via the web site above.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Kite Designer Update Site" url="http://dev.lucidcode.com.tr/update"/>
      <discovery label="LucidCode Home" url="http://www.lucidcode.com.tr"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.gef" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views" version="3.5.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.css.core" version="1.1.402" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.xml.core" version="1.1.503" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.xml.ui" version="1.1.103" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.html.core" version="1.1.404" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.sse.core" version="1.1.504" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.sse.ui" version="1.2.3" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="javax.servlet" version="2.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.6.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.commons.lang" version="2.3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.commons.io" version="2.0.1" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="tr.com.lucidcode.kite.eclipse.page.browser" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide" version="3.6.2" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.m2e.archetype.common" version="1.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.m2e.maven.runtime" version="1.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.expressions" version="3.4.200" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.m2e.core" version="1.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.m2e.core.ui" version="1.4.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jetty.util" version="7.6.15" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jetty.server" version="7.6.15" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jetty.http" version="7.6.15" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="tr.com.lucidcode.kite.eclipse.page.designer"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.4"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="tr.com.lucidcode.kite.eclipse.wizard.project"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.9"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="tr.com.lucidcode.kite.eclipse.wizard.page"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.3"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="tr.com.lucidcode.kite.eclipse.perspective"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="1.0.2"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
